{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879b01cfba6a787841ca8"},"product_asin":"B08HZCFNX1","QAs":[{"question":"Does it require both wifi and power plug in to make this bulb work? what if the wifi gets disconnected inbetween?","answer":"Yes both are required. if wifi gets disconnected then it will also work but can't control it without wifi.","votes":"0","username":"anonymous…","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does rgb bulb contain pure white light? like normal bulb? or it consists only colors?","answer":"YES , Pure white too ... Its a good buy !","votes":"0","username":"S.Sridharan","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we have to pair it again after electricity is out","answer":"No, we don't have to. The pairing need to do again only if the wifi network is changed or if you wish to connect it to any other network.","votes":"0","username":"Hareesh R","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about its durability? How long will it last if it is used daily on an average of 6 hours?","answer":"With steady electric supply it’s lasted more than 1 year with a usage of ~8 hours daily","votes":"0","username":"Arun","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get shades of white if i purchase RGB varient","answer":"Yes ofcourse","votes":"0","username":"anonymous…","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have camera installation process?","answer":"Sir, This is a bulb. So I am not sure what you are trying to do with camera with it.","votes":"0","username":"Amit Gore","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ios compatible?","answer":"Sir, you can install app on ios and use this bulb features. I am using it on iphone SE (2016) and iphone XR with iOS version 15.x","votes":"0","username":"Amit Gore","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879b31cfba6a787841cc9"},"product_asin":"B08BYJLB4Z","QAs":[{"question":"This is chargeable ?","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Harikrupa Electrical","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"If any defect happen under warranty, where i get replace?","answer":"I didn't get defects so I don't know the way about replacement, I you need please contact with Havells customer care.","votes":"0","username":"Soundararajan K L","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879b31cfba6a787841cd7"},"product_asin":"B071DQ34X8","QAs":[{"question":"This torch has Charging indicator","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Saifuddin Abbasali","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to charge the torch","answer":"At the back end there is 2 pin which is to be pushed out and attach it to the AC Socket and after recharging push the two pin inside. Red light will glow while recharging which is located on the side of torch.","votes":"0","username":"Saifuddin Abbasali","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879b61cfba6a787841cf9"},"product_asin":"B08WLT729V","QAs":[{"question":"Battery backup hour time","answer":"There is none","votes":"0","username":"Sreyashkar Datta","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much years warranty","answer":"1 Year Warrenty","votes":"0","username":"AKSHAR HARDWARE & ELECTRICALS","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879b71cfba6a787841cfe"},"product_asin":"B01L56DSKG","QAs":[{"question":"Minimum full charging time ?","answer":"About three hours.","votes":"0","username":"Hari Krishnan","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to change  content  number","answer":"All good","votes":"0","username":"Priyasondhi","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are the correct dimensions of this torch?","answer":"Helpful","votes":"0","username":"Priyasondhi","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Charger vasthundha radha","answer":"Excellent","votes":"0","username":"Priyasondhi","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this made in india?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Priyasondhi","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"How long will the battery last in full charge","answer":"3-4 hours approximately","votes":"0","username":"K. Rajesh Sundaram","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879b71cfba6a787841d04"},"product_asin":"B07P7H51FR","QAs":[{"question":"Is this bulb suitable for study?","answer":"If you are planning to use it in Study Lamp, then I will say 'No, its not for study lamp. Its too bright and needs to be use for room. Not in Study Table Lamp'. If you are going to use in room, then enough light for study.","votes":"0","username":"Anup Kumar","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879b91cfba6a787841d07"},"product_asin":"B08HZDLGF3","QAs":[{"question":"Can we decrease the brightness?","answer":"Yes you can . for what it is its quite complete in all the functions. I have my two going on and off at a set time every evening and that was simple to set up/","votes":"0","username":"RMAD","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"does it work without Wi-Fi","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Chandra Shekhar Singh","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it work without router","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"V K","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can we switch color from white to others?","answer":"App","votes":"0","username":"V K","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we create group or family in 'digi smart' app?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Chandra Shekhar Singh","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879ba1cfba6a787841d0e"},"product_asin":"B071DQ3TS5","QAs":[{"question":"This torch has Charging indicator","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Saifuddin Abbasali","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to charge the torch","answer":"At the back end there is 2 pin which is to be pushed out and attach it to the AC Socket and after recharging push the two pin inside. Red light will glow while recharging which is located on the side of torch.","votes":"0","username":"Saifuddin Abbasali","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879bb1cfba6a787841d11"},"product_asin":"B08WPJSXTF","QAs":[{"question":"जरुरत ना होनेपर बंद कर सकते है ?","answer":"हाँ, लेकिन जब सप्लाई आ रही हो तब।","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can we turn off while not in use?","answer":"Just off it's plug","votes":"0","username":"Haryana Traders M. 9354962971","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879bd1cfba6a787841d15"},"product_asin":"B08HZB57RX","QAs":[{"question":"Can we decrease the brightness?","answer":"Yes you can . for what it is its quite complete in all the functions. I have my two going on and off at a set time every evening and that was simple to set up/","votes":"0","username":"RMAD","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"does it work without Wi-Fi","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Chandra Shekhar Singh","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it work without router","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"V K","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can we switch color from white to others?","answer":"App","votes":"0","username":"V K","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we create group or family in 'digi smart' app?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Chandra Shekhar Singh","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879c01cfba6a787841d21"},"product_asin":"B016VYAWA6","QAs":[{"question":"Is it chargeable with sunlight","answer":"No, it's got USB connection for normal power supply.","votes":"0","username":"supradip r.","date":"2022-07-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the charging time and what is the working time","answer":"It doesn't have charging facility. It plug n switch on.","votes":"0","username":"supradip r.","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"sleek table lamp price range of Rs.5000/-","answer":"I have purchased at Rs 889/- This much I know.","votes":"0","username":"Swami Apteshananda","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Where can I find the serial number ?","answer":"At the bottom there is model number etc. Below QR code there is long digit number. This may be serial number. I am not sure.","votes":"0","username":"Swami Apteshananda","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879c01cfba6a787841d24"},"product_asin":"B08J4N441J","QAs":[{"question":"How much range??","answer":"70 meters to above","votes":"0","username":"Shubham D.","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"It have solar??","answer":"No solar charging","votes":"0","username":"Sankar Raghavan","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How long battery lasting, is it possible to change the battery","answer":"Battery life is good.... different mode ls of light available","votes":"0","username":"Sankar Raghavan","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have purchased the item on 21st March 2022. Now while charging the indicator is not glowing. What is the period of warranty for this product?","answer":"One Year From date you Register, if not Register? You have to go for Authorized Service center.","votes":"0","username":"R RAGHUPATHI","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this lighting torch be used for forest camping and how many meter distance can the light be beamed? Thanks.","answer":"Yes...atleast 20 mtrs","votes":"0","username":"Sankar Raghavan","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"I receive this torch without philips logo ,there is no company name on it. is it original or duplicate?","answer":"The only ne I received has a logo however when ever a brand sells their… they do emboss the logo if it does not have its duplicate for sure","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"How i know it's fully charge after 5to6 hours indicator glow any different colour???","answer":"Very bad","votes":"0","username":"Atul","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many days we have warranty for this product?","answer":"Very bad","votes":"0","username":"Atul","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879c01cfba6a787841d2a"},"product_asin":"B07XD8G2HR","QAs":[{"question":"I dont have wifi how can i join it with my mobiles hostspot from single mobile","answer":"Yes you can do it. If you can't do this see the YouTube tutorial for more information.","votes":"0","username":"Susnata Parua","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Unable to pair. Did all the efforts as mentioned like switching on off multiple times but no help?!!!","answer":"Not working with wiz... Waste of money... No support from wiz app...","votes":"0","username":"Amit Prajapati","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Including inverter bulb option there?","answer":"Oh yes , of course","votes":"0","username":"Ricky N.","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will this bulb turn on instantly when switched on using regular switch? Or does it take time to connect to wifi router after turning on manual switch?","answer":"The bulb will turn on instantly. However, it takes about half a minute to connect to the internet. And only then you can control it as a smart bulb. Hope this helps..","votes":"0","username":"Nitin Mishra","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can you control this with wifi available in my smart phone?","answer":"You can control it with your phone, only if the bulb is connected to a router or hotspot of another mobile, not with the mobile you want to control the bulb with.","votes":"0","username":"Sayantan Biswas","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it generate brown and black colours?","answer":"It can generate shades of brown but not black","votes":"0","username":"Joseph David","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this rechargeable","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Rohit Sharma","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Difficulty in pairing the bulb though wifi connection is good. How to solve the issue","answer":"Worst smart bulb, chinese bulb.. contact to Philips","votes":"0","username":"rakesh kumar","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ye sale phle offer dete h, after booking order Cancle le dete h..Why?","answer":"Because stock runs out","votes":"0","username":"Sayantan Biswas","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it work like normal bulb like in normal bulb you turn on/off siwth and normal bulb work so it work like that?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Shabbir Rupawalla","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can dim the bulb?","answer":"Yes we can dim the bulb and also change custom Colors.","votes":"0","username":"Shael","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Once we schedule the time in app, will it required the app installed mobile in same wifi network? if the device is far... ?","answer":"The mobile can be anywhere in the world but the smart bulb should be connected to wifi... You can turn it on from anyplace near or far","votes":"0","username":"Joseph David","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i control from another house","answer":"Yes only if the bulb is connected to wifi","votes":"0","username":"BIJU V","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How long the bulb last ?","answer":"I'm using approx from a year and nothing has happened to the bulb. Working properly.","votes":"0","username":"Nidhi Kapadia","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"It’s Waterproof","answer":"Yes but I don't recommend you to dip it in the water.","votes":"0","username":"Susnata Parua","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use 13 hours per day","answer":"Yes. Can be kept on while charging . Discharge time is 4hrs.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"It automatically turns on and change colours due to changing voltages not good for indian conditions","answer":"It changes to colors of ur choice with the mobile app..na not thro changing voltages","votes":"0","username":"LogSiv","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ambent light","answer":"Will not recommend this as this bulb is not able to connect to wifi and there is no support from wiz app","votes":"0","username":"Amit Prajapati","date":"2022-08-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can lit the bulb using the app while the switchis off ?","answer":"nope the switch should be always on to  control thru app 🥲 you need home broadband to work perfectly overall good light for 700rs","votes":"0","username":"Alphin","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879c21cfba6a787841d38"},"product_asin":"B09M72TK2J","QAs":[{"question":"Why bulb flicker when power off","answer":"May be due to earthing fault or mains / live phase has gone directly to bulb & neutral phase through switch.","votes":"0","username":"Abhay Singh Shekhawat","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether available in yellow color?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Abhay Singh Shekhawat","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Emergency bulb warrenty kitni hai","answer":"1","votes":"0","username":"Akshay","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the warranty on this product?","answer":"Rechargeable  1 year warranty","votes":"0","username":"Sadam","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cash on delivery","answer":"Yes sure","votes":"0","username":"Sadam","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"It does not operate on inverter mode when power supply switch off","answer":"It's update automatically worked","votes":"0","username":"Sadam","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty number of years","answer":"No warranty","votes":"0","username":"Ramkumar Roj","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"what lumen in main","answer":"up to 800 lumens on the main power line.","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"what lumen in battery","answer":"50% lumen output on battery,","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Generator back up ( manual) line also it works?","answer":"Automatically worked","votes":"0","username":"Sadam","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it remain at 8 watts after the power goes off?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ajs jhala","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any switch in bulb for turn it off","answer":"No, their is no switch.","votes":"0","username":"Santosh","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any switch in bulb for turn it off","answer":"It's operaated from the main light switch .","votes":"0","username":"Ajs jhala","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How we identify that the bulb is fully charged ?","answer":"I think automatic cut off is provided in the bulb itself.","votes":"0","username":"M GOPALA KRISHNA","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879c31cfba6a787841d42"},"product_asin":"B0191QS9MO","QAs":[{"question":"is this thread bulb ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"P N","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879c41cfba6a787841d47"},"product_asin":"B09JZ1MSF6","QAs":[{"question":"How to keep the light in atomic switch on mode","answer":"It's not an automatic thing","votes":"0","username":"Rashmi","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it switch on atomic when power goes out","answer":"Noo it won't","votes":"0","username":"Rashmi","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the size of thr lamp","answer":"8 to 10 inch approx.","votes":"0","username":"Souren G.","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the light switch on immediately as the power goes of","answer":"8 to 10 8nch approx","votes":"0","username":"Souren G.","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"In the video describing the product it was mentioned that the AC charging cable is included with the product. Is it really included or not?","answer":"Yes it is included.","votes":"0","username":"Suman Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to charge? Is there any way to charge","answer":"USB chord is provided with the package for charging from external output socket.","votes":"0","username":"Suman Chakraborty","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879c51cfba6a787841d4d"},"product_asin":"B09DGNTS7G","QAs":[{"question":"Is the light of the lamp replaceable?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"sandeep","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it aslo work without battery, or when the battery get damaged","answer":"This is USB-powered, not driven by battery.","votes":"0","username":"Mr N Bhattacharyya","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the brightness gets reduced as time passes by while discharging or it remains same until fully discharged?","answer":"No when battery discharged brightness will be decrease.","votes":"0","username":"Vinod y.","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the lamp adjustable only in a straight angle or is it rotatable adjustable as well?","answer":"It's adjustable in all the directions...360°","votes":"0","username":"Riya sinha","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"For how much time will it last when fully charged and operated on minimum brightness?","answer":"On minimum brightness it'll last upto 4-5 hrs .. depending on daily use.","votes":"0","username":"Riya sinha","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"I received the product without power cable. How can I get the cable. Without it it's not charging!","answer":"You can ask for the one in customer support.","votes":"0","username":"Riya sinha","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"how long dose the lamp work after the  battery is fully charged","answer":"It works perfectly for about 3hrs when fully charged.","votes":"0","username":"Riya sinha","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which model is better? Philips skyy or philips orbit??","answer":"With the constant use of Philips orbit, I can say it is one of the best .","votes":"0","username":"Riya sinha","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why the charger cable is not connecting ?","answer":"Connect by placy correct position of charging pin","votes":"0","username":"Devanshu P.","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Battery fully charged but still not working without being plugged in usb.","answer":"Call to customer care","votes":"0","username":"Devanshu P.","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What to do when bulb is fused??","answer":"There is no bulb is this lamp. It is an led ring light that you charge through a usb cable.","votes":"0","username":"Regular_Amazon_Buyer","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879c51cfba6a787841d51"},"product_asin":"B08YRM5B41","QAs":[{"question":"Can it produce darker colours like brown and black coloured lights?","answer":"NO this is cool blue and warm white only glow.","votes":"0","username":"VINOTHKUMAR M","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"how do I claim warranty?","answer":"Call customers care","votes":"0","username":"VINOTHKUMAR M","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there is a rgbww version of this light?","answer":"Currently it has only version of white colours. For multicolor, you can buy our other Wiz bulbs of 9w, 10w or 12w.","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many colours it supports ?","answer":"Cool white and warm white only","votes":"0","username":"VINOTHKUMAR M","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it work with the Smart Life app?","answer":"Yes it's working","votes":"0","username":"dharmateja","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879c81cfba6a787841d5b"},"product_asin":"B07X922QQV","QAs":[{"question":"I'll be on vacation , so the bulb can be controlled remotely?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Fliker free?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Rajeev","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the new product work with 5Ghz WiFi network?","answer":"Yes. Will have to do manual pairing","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Rajeev","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"does this bulb support the apple home kit?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I control on off through a external switch or dimmer, and while doing so, will it retain its previous set colour that was done in the app?","answer":"Not sure about external dimmer. But using a switch is the same effect as a power failure. There is a setting in the app that controls the power failure behaviour.","votes":"0","username":"Luckyfluke","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can more than one bulb be controlled together as a group lighting?","answer":"Yes, you can control them from Wiz application on your mobile and once setup is done on your phone you can add your family members too so that they can also use it, they just need to download the application. You can simply create rooms just like we create a folder for files and add number of bulbs in that room and like wise other rooms as well in the house.You can also setup a timer for all these bulbs to Turn ON and Turn OFF automatically. Never turn of the bulbs directly from main power switch, just control it from the Wiz Application so that It can automatically turn On and Off as per timer.In case of power cut it automatically connects with App and WiFi. When power will restore it, you just have to turn the bulb off from App.see less","votes":"0","username":"Ankur Yadav","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have hue bridge and bulbs purchase from usa. if i buy these new bulbs and connect with usa hue bridge. is it going to work?","answer":"I doubt, it will not work ,because you need to step down the voltage ed first as USAis supplying 110 volts ,","votes":"0","username":"Yenvee","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879c81cfba6a787841d63"},"product_asin":"B014IRNDEK","QAs":[{"question":"Can we use it during loadshedding???","answer":"NO","votes":"0","username":"sreekumar","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879c81cfba6a787841d65"},"product_asin":"B00UHF3XDO","QAs":[{"question":"How much watt bulb needed for a room of 10 x 10 feets?","answer":"9 watts","votes":"0","username":"KDV","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879c91cfba6a787841d69"},"product_asin":"B01N148DEG","QAs":[{"question":"It was s rechargeble , in case it is how many hours it will glow","answer":"Not Rechargeable","votes":"0","username":"ARVIND","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it alexa enabled ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Debashis De","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"One piece didn't work when opened and tried yesterday. How can I claim company's promised warranty ?","answer":"Good results","votes":"0","username":"Jogender Singh","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have ordered two Philips led tube 4ft,it is very sorry to say that I have denied dilivery today because the seller dispatched one led tube Wipro bra","answer":"Totally wrong","votes":"0","username":"Jogender Singh","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879ca1cfba6a787841d6d"},"product_asin":"B097MZ9SV3","QAs":[{"question":"Can we plug it to a regular bulb socket","answer":"worst product  power backup poor....warranty cant caim","votes":"0","username":"sethu","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879ca1cfba6a787841d71"},"product_asin":"B07XQ3MQC7","QAs":[{"question":"Is it useful for a student to read when electricity's gone?","answer":"Useful but for only 15 minute.very poor battery backup","votes":"0","username":"Danish Akhtar","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used as emergency light, which switches on automatically during power failure","answer":"Nope, I don’t think so it’s more like a table lamp plus torch","votes":"0","username":"Mustafiz","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Charing cable damage","answer":"There is no charging cable but a 2 pin plugin point","votes":"0","username":"Saifuddin charbiwala…","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How will i know it is fully charged? I put it on charging and indicator is red ..Will indicator color change when it is fully charged  ?","answer":"No it doesn’t change color","votes":"0","username":"Saifuddin charbiwala…","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warnty years???","answer":"Six months warranty is there and 7days Regular Product replacement through amazon is there. thats all.","votes":"0","username":"Alampally","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it returnable if not found suitable","answer":"Yes think so","votes":"0","username":"Saifuddin charbiwala…","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879cb1cfba6a787841d7a"},"product_asin":"B07WHBT1BQ","QAs":[{"question":"can we change brightness of the light ?","answer":"Yes you can regulate nesss and even temprature.","votes":"0","username":"Subu W.","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it support Google home mini speaker?","answer":"It is WiFi & Alexa enabled I'm not sure about Google home but should work.","votes":"0","username":"Subu W.","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have RGB colors","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Subu W.","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much warranty","answer":"6mths","votes":"0","username":"Subu W.","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many years of warranty","answer":"06 month's","votes":"0","username":"Subu W.","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is colour tempreture changeable bulb?????","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Subu W.","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it work with Alexa?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Subu W.","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Work with google nest mini","answer":"No experience with Google but should work","votes":"0","username":"Subu W.","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it work with smarlife or tuyasmart app ?","answer":"No. It has its own app \"Syska smart home\"\"","votes":"0","username":"naushad","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Indoor  or  outdoor","answer":"One can use depending on the need we have installed outdoor.","votes":"0","username":"Subu W.","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879cc1cfba6a787841d83"},"product_asin":"B01DNPUHA6","QAs":[{"question":"How much is Warranted period?","answer":"1 year","votes":"0","username":"H S Trading Hub","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879d01cfba6a787841d88"},"product_asin":"B07ND7ZLVN","QAs":[{"question":"Is this light is not charging lights?","answer":"It doesn't require charging. It is a normal light bulb that can be fitted in a normal holder. It is powerful enough to light up an entire  room.","votes":"0","username":"Bijit","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it rechable","answer":"no it is not rechargeable","votes":"0","username":"NELS","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879d11cfba6a787841d8a"},"product_asin":"B07PG9Q4T7","QAs":[{"question":"Why this bulb blinks light when switch is off ?","answer":"Go for replacement , bulb is defective.","votes":"0","username":"Subham Kumar","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"how to turn it off immediately boss! don't want it to run on all the time after I turn off the wall switch and want to sleep!!! ?","answer":"This is not smart bulb","votes":"0","username":"Subham Kumar","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"What happens on day time? How will we switch off the light?","answer":"By switch","votes":"0","username":"Subham Kumar","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Switch off करने पर भी जलेगा क्या?","answer":"Nhi","votes":"0","username":"Akash sharma","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"When i turn off mcb, the bulb switched on, but when actual power cut happened, it was not working even though the switch was on. is it some default?","answer":"Switch off and switch on couple of times.","votes":"0","username":"Gajanan Hegde","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"I bought it in February but now it is bad, what should I do?","answer":"Only with AC volte brightness is more , otherwise its normal light","votes":"0","username":"Kiran Jannu","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Syska 7 watts b22 led white emergency bulb, pack of 1 sold by: etrade online return eligible through 05-mar-2022   500.00 new","answer":"May be, if you have preserved original Amazon packing.","votes":"0","username":"Gajanan Hegde","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Where we get charchable battery .it is at amezon??","answer":"It's light contains inbuilt battery 🔋","votes":"0","username":"Raj babu N","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Where we get charchable battery .it is at amezon??","answer":"Forget chargeable battery,the light is not working properly  n not responding fir warranty also.Just cheating only","votes":"0","username":"SAILENDRA THAKURIA","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879d11cfba6a787841d9d"},"product_asin":"B07X7JYPJS","QAs":[{"question":"while charging it's brightness increases..Can i use it while charging it all the time??","answer":"Yes, definitely bro...","votes":"0","username":"Tekram Dhruw","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many hours of battery life on different modes of lighting?","answer":"2:30hrs approximately high mode","votes":"0","username":"Tekram Dhruw","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i run this lamp on AC??","answer":"No need to waste your money onthis product, that's all I say.","votes":"0","username":"Stuti","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Just received the lamp. But It does not turn on. I've also tried turning it on by connecting it to the power supply.","answer":"Don't waste your money","votes":"0","username":"Stuti","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we charge this lamp with 32W mobile charger.. plzz reply","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Stuti","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this glare free ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Stuti","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do you provide charger for charging. If not then which charger to use?","answer":"No charger.","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep S Naik","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"When stock will  available","answer":"Yess","votes":"0","username":"Tekram Dhruw","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Battery backup time","answer":"i have not used it continiously. But can give approx 5 to 6 hours.","votes":"0","username":"pradeep kumar arya","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879d11cfba6a787841da6"},"product_asin":"B08BKX2XMY","QAs":[{"question":"Is it white light or yellow light?","answer":"White","votes":"0","username":"sujit sah","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can the light be changed?","answer":"Yes it's brightness can be adjusted but colour can't be changed. But has a very less backup time( less than 2 hours)","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is syska tl 751 8l better than this one?","answer":"Yeah absolutely i fell it is better , syska one is very bright ..","votes":"0","username":"Sujan sekh","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Battery backup ?","answer":"At full brightness will give u around 30 min backup , I will recommend to use continous power supply","votes":"0","username":"Hercule poirot","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Return the product","answer":"Its an amazing product, return for what?","votes":"0","username":"S S Maan 01262354611","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it in charging","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Hercule poirot","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is its total height from bottom to top","answer":"approx. 1 and half ft.","votes":"0","username":"S S Maan 01262354611","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have cool white and warm white options? Which one, if only one is available","answer":"have only warm white light option.","votes":"0","username":"S S Maan 01262354611","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to see if it is fully charged ?","answer":"there is no option how to see, but its take 6 - 7 Hrs. to fully charge.","votes":"0","username":"S S Maan 01262354611","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many days for delivery?","answer":"Depends on your location and availability, check with your PIN code.","votes":"0","username":"S S Maan 01262354611","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is battery covered in warranty ?","answer":"6 months.","votes":"0","username":"S S Maan 01262354611","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Service centre mobile number to repair","answer":"Check on Syska site.","votes":"0","username":"S S Maan 01262354611","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can i repair it bcoz its touch controls are not working. i have bought it 6-7 months ago.😭😭😭","answer":"Contact syska service center.","votes":"0","username":"S S Maan 01262354611","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"There is no charging cable in my box","answer":"Contact Seller or retailer.","votes":"0","username":"S S Maan 01262354611","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the Lumen for the lights?","answer":"upto 6000","votes":"0","username":"S S Maan 01262354611","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the life span of this Led bulb?","answer":"Years of years.","votes":"0","username":"S S Maan 01262354611","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Battery is replaceable","answer":"yes.","votes":"0","username":"S S Maan 01262354611","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"As it claims, 9 hours of easy usage on medium adaptability, how accurate is that? Also can i use the lamp while it's on charging mode?","answer":"I have been using the lamp while charging as I need it to be on high setting. However not sure about the long term effects of such usage","votes":"0","username":"Omkar Lavangad","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879d41cfba6a787841dce"},"product_asin":"B00W94GPTU","QAs":[{"question":"Do you have warranty and how long","answer":"No there is no warranty on it .actually they r cheep bulbs. I no money wasting but when u go market every one says his one is best .fed up and went this road. Came on time and so for waking ok","votes":"0","username":"mahajan sajad","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty kitni hai?","answer":"1 year","votes":"0","username":"DealWill™","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879d51cfba6a787841dd7"},"product_asin":"B08BKWMBBJ","QAs":[{"question":"Is it fire resistant?","answer":"Obviously NOO!!","votes":"0","username":"Prabir Das","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which is better Syska 12w or Philps 12w","answer":"both are better go for better price","votes":"0","username":"Sushant kumar","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"After delivery how much time limit to return this","answer":"You will get only 7 days for return, and replacement. Don't replace it, just return it. Syska is the worst product.","votes":"0","username":"Prabir Das","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to connect syska with another device","answer":"You can only connect Syska With Google Assistant, Alexa, and IFTT(a bit complex).","votes":"0","username":"Prabir Das","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hi so I have changed my wifi and the bulb is not reacting to that. It shows offline. I have tried to reset it and then connect but it does not repond.","answer":"Steps to Fix it:-Step 1: Switch ON and OFF the bulb THREE times (Check The bulb is blinking Rapidly)Step 2: Open The AppStep 3: Remove the device from the listStep 4: Now try to Setup the bulbNOTE: If your WiFi is a 5g router, then it will not connect, because this bulb only supports 2.4 GHz wifi band. To connect it with wifi, you have to change band in wifi router settings.see less","votes":"0","username":"Prabir Das","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"The colours are not changing","answer":"Try reset it.","votes":"0","username":"Prabir Das","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"my bulb not working how to get replacement","answer":"Search on Youtube.","votes":"0","username":"Prabir Das","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to integrate with Home Assistant?","answer":"Depends on which assistant you want to use. check the user manual of the manufacturer.","votes":"0","username":"Prabir Das","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"It shows ‘device connection timeout’. How can it be fixed?","answer":"Try to connect the bulb by keeping the Phone and bulb near the router in the same room as near as possible. after successful pairing, you can change the room.","votes":"0","username":"Prabir Das","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Without router can we control LED bulb with   mobile wifi?","answer":"Yes, but you will need two devices. One for hotspot, one for connecting the bulb. Note -  you cannot connect the bulb using one machine, as the second device will do the job of a WiFi router.","votes":"0","username":"Prabir Das","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it compatible with Google home nest mini?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"MANIKANDAN K.","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it compatible with Google home nest mini?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Prabir Das","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cover already open and no proper response my order please rectify my order","answer":"Just Return it","votes":"0","username":"Prabir Das","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"I can take legal against compny and amazon , regarding bed services?","answer":"just for 300 Rs bulb. Just return or replace it. Don't take such decisions","votes":"0","username":"Prabir Das","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Haw can i contect to customer care to regarding warranty ?","answer":"Search  contact us in amazon app","votes":"0","username":"Prabir Das","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i operate it with multiple mobile phones??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vijay Sharma","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it's red and blue colour provide enough spectrum for indoor plants?","answer":"When you use this lamp in RGB colour mode, it's lumens drops drastically as compared to white. Please take note of this before buying.","votes":"0","username":"Prithvisingh","date":"2022-08-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879d61cfba6a787841de5"},"product_asin":"B0774LDZ2V","QAs":[{"question":"वारंटी कहां से मिलेगी","answer":"Syska company se","votes":"0","username":"Shani jaishwal","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What bulb today","answer":"Nice","votes":"0","username":"Jatin chauhan","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"We have ordered pack of 6 but received only 5 and one empty box .","answer":"Return it.","votes":"0","username":"Sumit","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"amazon par warranty hai to wapas nahi kar sakte hain kya","answer":"Kar sakte ho.","votes":"0","username":"Sumit","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to claim warranty?","answer":"Call syska customer support.","votes":"0","username":"Sumit","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warnti kon dega","answer":"Syska.","votes":"0","username":"Sumit","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879d71cfba6a787841def"},"product_asin":"B08BKWMMBP","QAs":[{"question":"can we use this when charging on","answer":"Yes! Use it always charging on. It just works  like inverter when no electricity it continued lightning your desk for hr.","votes":"0","username":"Anangpal singh rathore","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"How mah of its battery?","answer":"Almost 1 hr max with full brightness.","votes":"0","username":"Anangpal singh rathore","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to know battery fully charged..i charged more than 6 hours but still charging light on","answer":"It doesn't indicate full charge ........light will always on if you put it on charging ............u should charge it six to seven hours......","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Gupta","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whom to conntact for any issue during warranty period","answer":"Syska Toll Free Number 1800-102-8787","votes":"0","username":"GURetails","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Battery backup?","answer":"4 h","votes":"0","username":"Abhik Roy","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the height of the stand of the light?","answer":"25cm","votes":"0","username":"Anoop V","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need to get an Invoice for the order,","answer":"You would raise one from the order section in your profile","votes":"0","username":"Anoop V","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Return policy or not","answer":"Yes available, but again it depend on the seller","votes":"0","username":"Anoop V","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use it during charging time?","answer":"Yes of course","votes":"0","username":"Anoop V","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use syska led with Direct current always ? Is it harmful for the battery life or the quality of the led ?","answer":"I m using like that, since the battery back up is not that good","votes":"0","username":"Anoop V","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to avail warranty","answer":"Call customer care for more info","votes":"0","username":"Anoop V","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879eb1cfba6a787841e37"},"product_asin":"B08H6BJF8Y","QAs":[{"question":"Is this product chargeable","answer":"No not chargeable. It is normal tube light.","votes":"0","username":"FRANCISCO X C FERNANDES","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it charging tube","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Paulraj G.","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does product have warranty?","answer":"Yes,One year warrenty","votes":"0","username":"Paulraj G.","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can i claim my warranty . And also i have mail bajaj 10 days ago no reply at please help me hiw can i get warranty","answer":"You better contact the Amazon customer care service to know the details about claiming the warrenty","votes":"0","username":"Paulraj G.","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"I had bought this product and delivered. 3 august but after 14 august about 18 august product is fused and i have 1 year warranty from bajaj","answer":"You claim warrenty through registering with company website or with Amazon customer care service","votes":"0","username":"Paulraj G.","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"its a inverter light or nor","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Paulraj G.","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"is this a tubelight ? can be used in normal plate","answer":"It doesn't require plate. It came with 2 clips just put them on wall and it's fixed","votes":"0","username":"perbhat","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879ed1cfba6a787841e3d"},"product_asin":"B01JOHQJMM","QAs":[{"question":"what is the power factor of the bulb? is it more than 0.9?","answer":"Yes off course power factor should be above 0.9 to low power consumption.","votes":"0","username":"Mohammed Azam","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879f21cfba6a787841e47"},"product_asin":"B0866HY6B3","QAs":[{"question":"If needed, how can the battery be replaced?","answer":"By openning its base  but it hasnt need to be replaced uptill now about one year","votes":"0","username":"abhishek tiwari","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879fd1cfba6a787841e6f"},"product_asin":"B08TWT2DQ3","QAs":[{"question":"Does it come with warranty card","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Haryana Traders M. 9354962971","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is charger included?","answer":"Yes with Charging Wire","votes":"0","username":"Haryana Traders M. 9354962971","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879fe1cfba6a787841e73"},"product_asin":"B09RVYZM3W","QAs":[{"question":"Does it come with Warranty??","answer":"1yr warranty","votes":"0","username":"Naresh…","date":"2022-07-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is both are inveter bulbs and how much period of warrenty for both bulbs.","answer":"1yr","votes":"0","username":"Naresh…","date":"2022-07-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to on when light go how it on automatically or have any switch","answer":"It's automatically on when power off no need to enable/off switch","votes":"0","username":"Surya kumari","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879fe1cfba6a787841e77"},"product_asin":"B07SGCDWL5","QAs":[{"question":"May it use as regular bulb?","answer":"Yes. A very useful product. When power goes off the brightness is about half and when it is restored, the bulb glows at normal brightness. You can switch on and off even when the power supply is not there.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"will the bulb damaged / fused if it is wet by rain water while using on outdoors?","answer":"This bulb is not compatible to be used in outdoors","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"will the bulb got fuse if wet by rain water or not?","answer":"yes, it will","votes":"0","username":"Asok N S","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use it at open area? outdoor? will it work under rain water?","answer":"yes, It will work in open area but brightness will not be sufficient. 10W is less for open area.","votes":"0","username":"Neha Singh","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Bulb not powering off with button off, tried in 3 different holders, when power button on glows more and button off glows less.","answer":"It is wireing problem check  phase,netural and earthing","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How i will get the Warranty?","answer":"One year","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is battery life. I mean how many years it will work?","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879ff1cfba6a787841e7c"},"product_asin":"B016VYB624","QAs":[{"question":"Is it chargeable with sunlight","answer":"No, it's got USB connection for normal power supply.","votes":"0","username":"supradip r.","date":"2022-07-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the charging time and what is the working time","answer":"It doesn't have charging facility. It plug n switch on.","votes":"0","username":"supradip r.","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"sleek table lamp price range of Rs.5000/-","answer":"I have purchased at Rs 889/- This much I know.","votes":"0","username":"Swami Apteshananda","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Where can I find the serial number ?","answer":"At the bottom there is model number etc. Below QR code there is long digit number. This may be serial number. I am not sure.","votes":"0","username":"Swami Apteshananda","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c879ff1cfba6a787841e7e"},"product_asin":"B0862GS4T8","QAs":[{"question":"how to turn it off (when not needed to be on for 4 hours or so, after power is turned off using switch)?","answer":"Yes.. You can switch it off when not needed..","votes":"0","username":"Anoop Verma","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to claim warranty?","answer":"Contact Phillips customer service.","votes":"0","username":"Kirandev TK","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to claim warranty, the light is working but not giving backup","answer":"Refer the box of the bulb and call at customer care","votes":"0","username":"Kirandev TK","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"I don't have inverter can I use without inverter if power cut happen it is run or not","answer":"Yes it will run. But you need to switch it ON, then only the sensor inside the bulb detect no current and will work with its battery inside.","votes":"0","username":"Kirandev TK","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"my 12 watt inverter bulb gets on automatically even when switch is off why ?","answer":"Defect in making. Return the bulb","votes":"0","username":"Pradip Maji","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can i replace whenever its get fuse during warranty","answer":"No exchange","votes":"0","username":"GORLE PRASAD","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we need to turn on the bulb for working?","answer":"yes,","votes":"0","username":"SantEnt","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any problem to led bulb how to warranty claim","answer":"Go to nearest care","votes":"0","username":"Pradip Maji","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Price at local shop for philips 12watt inverter lamp ₹470/-","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"GORLE PRASAD","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a way to test the inverter mode without waiting for power to go off?","answer":"Its very easy method. Take your bulb in left hand,wet your right hand any finger and then touch the bulb 2 nods with same finger. bulb become On.","votes":"0","username":"Vamshi Krishna","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we need an Inverter to charge this bulb or it charges itself automatically in the wall socket when the light has gone?","answer":"No need inverters. it charges itself automatically in the wall socket when the light is ON.","votes":"0","username":"Vamshi Krishna","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"My bulb got faulty before completion of 1year, now where can I get it replaced?","answer":"Call 8000507777 or write to support.philipsLightingIndia@signify.com","votes":"0","username":"SantEnt","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"will the bulb get damaged if wet by rain water?","answer":"It will be damage","votes":"0","username":"Vamshi Krishna","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do you pre-charge the batteries? How do I test if the bulb is working properly? Tried closing the circuit and the bulb does not lite up.","answer":"No pre charging. Wet your finger . close the curcuit. lights up.","votes":"0","username":"Vamshi Krishna","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have charged this bulb for 12 hours and yet it soesnt light when powwr goes.. how does it work ??","answer":"If it doesn't work then change the battery.","votes":"0","username":"Md GOLAM RASUL","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do the bulb glow when power is cut","answer":"Yes, it glow.","votes":"0","username":"Md GOLAM RASUL","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"What will happen if I connect both end by a metal ? Will it on battery back up mode?","answer":"If I connect both end by a metal  , it will glow.","votes":"0","username":"Md GOLAM RASUL","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या इलेक्ट्रिक रहने पर बल्ब का स्विच ऑन करने पर बल्ब इलेक्ट्रिक से जलेगा","answer":"हाँ","votes":"0","username":"अजय सिंह यादव","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to Claim the warranty when I bought a product from Amazon?","answer":"Just go through the respected product description ..to claim warranty and u may contact for.the customer service to the particular concern....","votes":"0","username":"Rushi n","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to get warranty on this bulb","answer":"Ask Amazon customer care, when you get trouble. I had purchased one Philips inverter bulb with nice Carton packing. The inverter bulb was upto my thinking. Second one ordered, the same Philips Inverter bulb. The packing was worst, in a simple brown cover, the consequence was the cover of the bulb has come out & being an engineer assembled myself & used. Informed Amazon on such a worst packing on my second order. Informed Amazon, no reply from them. Ofcourse We can't expect for every item Amazon responsible. Both are Amazon certified source. Hope the second source they should have black listed due to bad packing remark, I suppose in the absence of reply to me. Don't expect any warranty help or bad packing help from Amazon. Trust Amazon do the work. Super senior citizen feedbacksee less","votes":"0","username":"RAGA","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do we know this inverter bulb get charge fully? in day time","answer":"Trust the innovator, buy the bulb, switch ON for 8 to 10 hours &  follow the instructions. First purchased one, satisfied, second one also ordered & using. You don't try life cycle of the product. Use & enjoy the result. We love it. Replaced tubelights in Kitchen & dinning hall. Wonderful. Want to have one in drawing hall also. My findings in a methodical way as a super senior citizensee less","votes":"0","username":"RAGA","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"if the power will be cut the lamp is not working...Only 8months... Usages  I bought a two Philips reachable light..","answer":"The bulb has overcharge protection as well deep discharge protection. It takes care of power supply. Only thing what I found was for balanced power supply failure, working is smooth. For unbalanced power supply failure, function is not that good, means it won't light up on Switched OFF to ON condition. This is due to some current in neutral line. This is common in India ie, unbalanced mode in power failure at times. We can't help. Such condition occurs, switch off main, bulb will work. Then restore main, when supply returns. Findings from super senior citizen engineersee less","votes":"0","username":"RAGA","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"What mean the recharge cycle","answer":"Recharge cycle means charge / discharge cycle. I think they have given around 10000 cycle or more if I am correct. That's the quality test. It does not mean that it will fail. It is a result of sample test by supplier. Super senior citizen opinion","votes":"0","username":"RAGA","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"This bulb is giving light(ON) even when switch is turned down. Is there a way to exchange this?","answer":"Once charged, use like a normal bulb. But daily you switch ON for a some minimum duration to get keep go on the benefit. That's why you should in places like kitchen or dining hall or Drawing hall where usage is there. If you want the bulb in other places, remove the charged bulb & used it wherever you want. Amazon is selling a holder special type, wherein the charged bulb can be plugged & without any wiring you can switch On the bulb with the knob provided on the special holder. It costs only Rs 69/-. I want to order. But Amazon try to levy delivery charges inspite of order value is more than Rs 500. Sad part from Amazon. This special holder is boon to inverter bulb for moveable wirless mode. Great innovation, but Amazon exploits for Rs 69 cost + delivery cost. Not Happy. They should sell with bulb as a packagesee less","votes":"0","username":"RAGA","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87a011cfba6a787841e8b"},"product_asin":"B08FGMYVSC","QAs":[{"question":"What is charging time??","answer":"5-6 hrs.","votes":"0","username":"Anil","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"कितनी दूर तक रोशनी फेंकती है","answer":"200 mtr something","votes":"0","username":"Yogesh","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"how far the light will go?,... can we use it for lighting the road while walking at night?","answer":"its light is farther than conventional torch .,roughly if u r standing on a 3rd floor u can lit the ground easily","votes":"0","username":"Kalyan","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"are there charger?","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"Anil","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87a031cfba6a787841e99"},"product_asin":"B09B435VNR","QAs":[{"question":"Will it work on Indoor plants?","answer":"Offcourse yes but away. From water because that's not IP68 MEANS not water resistant","votes":"0","username":"LAXMI SALES_","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Once i setup all desire setting on app and then ill leave app and wifi, what it will continue to with setup or come to the white?","answer":"It will continue with what was configured","votes":"0","username":"Vishwas Gujar","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it start with same colour as last was switch off or it will be come to white?","answer":"Yes, on power ON it will have the same color which you have configured earlier.","votes":"0","username":"Vishwas Gujar","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the Wattage in low brightness? In low brightness will it consume less watt power?","answer":"Yes when use in dim light it's consumption low and in full 9w consum","votes":"0","username":"LAXMI SALES_","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is Fail-safe override from powered off from app condition. Please elucidate","answer":"App is for configuration. Run mode doesn't change unless it is re-configured.","votes":"0","username":"Vishwas Gujar","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87a041cfba6a787841ea7"},"product_asin":"B00IN23UIQ","QAs":[{"question":"Whether Remote control inclusion in fan box?","answer":"Yes, the box includes Fan and remote both.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want only remote for orient spectra celling fan led","answer":"You can contact the support email or phone number to get the remote","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Lost the remote need inly remote","answer":"Yes can contact support email or phone number from their website","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get only the remote..? As I have lost the previous one..","answer":"Yes can contact support number or email from their website","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"My orient fan remote is not working is it available online","answer":"Yes can contact support number or email from their website","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"My remote is not working is it available online","answer":"Yes can contact support number or email from their website","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to get replacement remote?","answer":"Yes can contact support number or email from their website","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87a171cfba6a787841f30"},"product_asin":"B00YU1E4UC","QAs":[{"question":"Guarantee for how many months","answer":"1 year warranty","votes":"0","username":"R K ENTERPRISES_","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87a191cfba6a787841f38"},"product_asin":"B08B3Z29S6","QAs":[{"question":"Will it work on Indoor plants?","answer":"Offcourse yes but away. From water because that's not IP68 MEANS not water resistant","votes":"0","username":"LAXMI SALES_","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Once i setup all desire setting on app and then ill leave app and wifi, what it will continue to with setup or come to the white?","answer":"It will continue with what was configured","votes":"0","username":"Vishwas Gujar","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it start with same colour as last was switch off or it will be come to white?","answer":"Yes, on power ON it will have the same color which you have configured earlier.","votes":"0","username":"Vishwas Gujar","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the Wattage in low brightness? In low brightness will it consume less watt power?","answer":"Yes when use in dim light it's consumption low and in full 9w consum","votes":"0","username":"LAXMI SALES_","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is Fail-safe override from powered off from app condition. Please elucidate","answer":"App is for configuration. Run mode doesn't change unless it is re-configured.","votes":"0","username":"Vishwas Gujar","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c87a1c1cfba6a787841f54"},"product_asin":"B016IGHO8K","QAs":[{"question":"Is this bulb suitable for ikea lamp?","answer":"Yes,may require low wattage bulb.","votes":"0","username":"Lak","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c9cad51cfba6a78785744e"},"product_asin":"B075F9Z6XB","QAs":[{"question":"How i claim warranty","answer":"Call to official customer support at Phillips for claiming warrenty. Source- Phillips executive","votes":"0","username":"Lakhan ahir","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62cdbf7b1cfba6a787895d43"},"product_asin":"B01DNPUHEW","QAs":[{"question":"How to claim warranty product not working after 8 months","answer":"Please talk or write to supplier","votes":"0","username":"Nayan M.","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Prime member through Tata sky- free delivery is possible.","answer":"Yes, it's possible!","votes":"0","username":"Customer","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"I havecasked for return as the product wont fit onto my holder.Given return pick up is on 3rd of Jan 21 but,i am still waiting for the refund?","answer":"Contact Amazon for further help on this!","votes":"0","username":"Customer","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"This product warranty","answer":"1 year manufacturer warranty for manufacturing defects!","votes":"0","username":"Customer","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62d456931cfba6a78798b310"},"product_asin":"B00MGF4YTU","QAs":[{"question":"Once the bulb is over with its life. Can we use the dock to fix any other bulb or is it also no use of?","answer":"It's use and throw","votes":"0","username":"Sunita","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62d84b121cfba6a787a22545"},"product_asin":"B09T37S9Y5","QAs":[{"question":"Can it be installed on wall bulb holder or need ceiling installation?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"prakash jay","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Should switch be in on always ?","answer":"Yes. The bulb will turn off after 1 min when no motion.","votes":"0","username":"Aparna","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"power cord required to ON or battery operated","answer":"It is like a normal bulb just put it in bulb holder :)","votes":"0","username":"INDIA","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it work during day time?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Bhave S S","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its come in 3W or 5W??","answer":"Check","votes":"0","username":"INDIA","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62dd910e1cfba6a787b0b770"},"product_asin":"B08563PR4F","QAs":[{"question":"Is it chargeable or inverter bulbs..??","answer":"They  are ordinary bulbs","votes":"0","username":"G Narayanamurthi","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the difference between B12 and B22","answer":"They  relates to different  holder types","votes":"0","username":"G Narayanamurthi","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wants in yellow bright colour","answer":"U will have to buy clear white or day light led bulb","votes":"0","username":"Mike_goa_india","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"}]}
